Summary _

Experienced technical leader, manager and engineer, with broad experience in building products from inception to delivery, using a wide variety of technologies. Proven ability to grow and develop teams, improve processes and lead to successful product delivery.

Experience

Splunk Seattle, WA

SENIOR DIRECTOR OF ENGINEERING, CORE SERVICES AND SEATTLE SITE LEAD

2013 - PRESENT

- Engineering leader for Core Services at Splunk, managing 80 engineers across three locations.
- · Site Lead for the Seattle office, drove office investment and growth from four people to over sixty today across multiple functions.
- Managed, hired and developed a team of engineers ranging in seniority from junior to principal engineers.
- Driving technical and product strategy for Splunk across multiple areas.
- Led development and architecture for several critical technical initiatives, including HTTP ingestion, Splunk's KV Store, and improvements to Splunk's manageability and scalability.
- Global engineering release lead for multiple releases of Splunk's flagship product, Splunk Enterprise.
- Initiated and drove multiple cross-organizational initiatives to improve Splunk's engineering process, such as source control, code reviews, continuous integration and interviewing.
- Regular interaction with customers for technical enablement, roadmap and support discussions.

Splunk Seattle, WA

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER 2011 - 2013

- Founding engineer of Splunk's Seattle, the first office out of the Bay Area.
- Led technical direction and architecture for our Developer Platform initiative, including Splunk's SDKs, Tooling and Web Framework.
- Lead developer for several of our SDKs and the Splunk Web Framework.

Microsoft Redmond, WA

SOFTWARE DESIGN ENGINEER II - TECHNICAL STRATEGY INCUBATION (MIDORI)

2008 - 2011

- Designed and implemented a capability-based security system for low-level resources in a next-generation operating system.
- Designing and implementing synergistic scenarios between OS and hypervisor, including enlightened video and debugging services.
- Involved in design and implementation of various aspects of system, from low-level subsystems to high-level applications and services.

Microsoft Redmond, WA

SOFTWARE DESIGN ENGINEER INTERN - MEDIA FOUNDATION/WINDOWS EXPERIENCE

Jun. 2007 - Aug. 2007

- · Developed multimedia playback scenario in Media Foundation and Windows Media Player, shipped as part of Windows 7.
- $\bullet \ \ \text{Implemented metadata solution through Media Foundation for new media format.}$

Education

University of Washington Seattle, WA

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE Sept. 2010 - June 2012

Brown University Providence, RI

B.Sc. in Computer Science, B.A. in Economics Sept. 2004 - May 2008

Oxford University Oxford, UK

Visiting Student at St. Edmund's Hall / Oxford Computing Laboratory

Jan. 2007 - June 2007

Speaking_

Apr 2012 **JSConf US** Scottsdale, AZ

Splunk + JavaScript: bringing your data to life

Realtime Big Data makes real data big time: https://youtu.be/r0TVWW8316E

ongoing **Splunk** USA

Multiple Splunk speaking engagements, audiences ranging from 10 to a 1000

Other

Languages English (Fluent), Hebrew (Fluent)

Awards Splunk BUILD MVP, Splunk Values Award - Innovation